<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <!-- Afflictions -->
  <afflictionname.flu>Flu</afflictionname.flu>
  <afflictiondescription.flu>The patient has a flu. In the long term, this can lead to near death experience.</afflictiondescription.flu>
  <afflictionname.fever>Fever</afflictionname.fever>
  <afflictiondescription.fever>The patient suffers from high temperatures inside his body. His immune system might need some external help to deal with diseases.</afflictiondescription.fever>
  <afflictionname.cancer>Cancer</afflictionname.cancer>
  <afflictiondescription.cancer>The patient suffers from cancer. The threat of death hanging over the patient requires timely treatment. In the worst case, a painful death awaits the patient.</afflictiondescription.cancer>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.cancer>Died from cancer</afflictioncauseofdeath.cancer>
  <afflictionname.spacerabies>Space rabies</afflictionname.spacerabies>
  <afflictiondescription.spacerabies>The patient is suffering from space rabies, an infection that probably came from a bite. Patient experiences blurry vision, increased movement speed, and the desire to physically hurt other living beings.</afflictiondescription.spacerabies>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.spacerabies>Died from rabies</afflictioncauseofdeath.spacerabies>
  <afflictionname.psyshock>Psychotic shock</afflictionname.psyshock>
  <afflictiondescription.psyshock>The patient begins to gradually go crazy and lose his mind. In the end, this can lead to the death of the patient.</afflictiondescription.psyshock>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.psyshock>Died from heavy stress</afflictioncauseofdeath.psyshock>
  <afflictionname.bloodpoisoning>Blood poisoning</afflictionname.bloodpoisoning>
  <afflictiondescription.bloodpoisoning>The result of a donor blood transfusion by an inexperienced doctor. Additional blood transfusion may be required.</afflictiondescription.bloodpoisoning>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.bloodpoisoning>Died from blood poisoning</afflictioncauseofdeath.bloodpoisoning>
  <afflictionname.severeinjury>Severe injury</afflictionname.severeinjury>
  <afflictiondescription.severeinjury>The limb is badly damaged. The patient is in severe pain.</afflictiondescription.severeinjury>
  <afflictionname.pain>Pain</afflictionname.pain>
  <afflictiondescription.pain>The patient suffers from intense pain that accumulates from injuries and bleeding. Prolonged high pain can cause disorientation or blackout.</afflictiondescription.pain>
  <afflictionname.severebleeding>Severe bleeding</afflictionname.severebleeding>
  <afflictiondescription.severebleeding>Open wound. The patient is in severe pain.</afflictiondescription.severebleeding>
  <!-- Items -->
  <entityname.antibioticpowder>Antibiotic powder</entityname.antibioticpowder>
  <entitydescription.antibioticpowder>Helps to create a cure to diseases. It's a medical component.</entitydescription.antibioticpowder>
  <entityname.vitaminpowder>Vitamin powder</entityname.vitaminpowder>
  <entitydescription.vitaminpowder>Helps to create the immune boosting medicine. It's a medical component.</entitydescription.vitaminpowder>
  <entityname.bloodsample>Blood sample</entityname.bloodsample>
  <entitydescription.bloodsample>A container filled with blood. Useful for crafting medicines.</entitydescription.bloodsample>
  <entityname.emptysyringe>Empty syringe</entityname.emptysyringe>
  <entitydescription.emptysyringe>An empty syringe. Useful for extracting fluids from bodies.</entitydescription.emptysyringe>
  <entityname.reagent>Reagent</entityname.reagent>
  <entitydescription.reagent>Useful for creating commom medicine. It's a medical component.</entitydescription.reagent>
  <entityname.liquidplasma>Liquid Plasma</entityname.liquidplasma>
  <entitydescription.liquidplasma>Useful for creating advanced medicine. It's an advanced medical component.</entitydescription.liquidplasma>
  <!-- Medicine -->
  <entityname.antibioticpills>Antibiotics</entityname.antibioticpills>
  <entitydescription.antibioticpills>Mild antibiotics in the form of pills. Help treat diseases.</entitydescription.antibioticpills>
  <entityname.vitaminpills>Vitamins</entityname.vitaminpills>
  <entitydescription.vitaminpills>Small pills that help the body recover. Tastes like a candy.</entitydescription.vitaminpills>
  <entityname.antipsychoticpills>Antipsychotics</entityname.antipsychoticpills>
  <entitydescription.antipsychoticpills>Reduces symptoms of psychosis associated with conditions like psychotic shock.</entitydescription.antipsychoticpills>
  <entityname.radiazine>Radiazine</entityname.radiazine>
  <entitydescription.radiazine>A syringe filled with an almost lethal composition, said to be able to cure cancer and radiation.</entitydescription.radiazine>
  <entityname.rabiesvaccine>Rabies vaccine</entityname.rabiesvaccine>
  <entitydescription.rabiesvaccine>A syringe filled with a mixture of blood and other powerful components provides resistance to rabies. Saves life in the early stages of the disease.</entitydescription.rabiesvaccine>
  <entityname.vitaminsoulution>Vitamin solution</entityname.vitaminsoulution>
  <entitydescription.vitaminsoulution>A highly effective, versatile high-concentration solution of vitamins that allows you to get the patient out of almost any difficult situation. Prior to the development of combat stimulants, it was considered the main means of performing the functions of a combat stimulant. This medication is known for its strong side effects.</entitydescription.vitaminsoulution>
  <entityname.compressionbandage>Compression bandage</entityname.compressionbandage>
  <entitydescription.compressionbandage>A bandage, specially designed to treat broken bones, but also can be used to treat severe bleedings.</entitydescription.compressionbandage>
  <entityname.donorbloodpack>Donor Blood Pack</entityname.donorbloodpack>
  <entitydescription.donorbloodpack>Made from raw donor blood, the pack heals blood loss.</entitydescription.donorbloodpack>
  <entityname.antibloodpills>Osimilin</entityname.antibloodpills>
  <entitydescription.antibloodpills>The drug, which slows down slightly metabolism. Increases blood pressure and the patient's chances of surviving heavy blood loss and bleeding. Paramedics are advised.</entitydescription.antibloodpills>
  <entityname.stasissolution>Cryoxadone Solution</entityname.stasissolution>
  <entitydescription.stasissolution>A cool mixture in a bag capable of introducing a patient into a trans close to cryonic sleep for a short time. Used only by experienced paramedics!</entitydescription.stasissolution>
  <entityname.antioxygenlow>Chemical Oxygen</entityname.antioxygenlow>
  <entitydescription.antioxygenlow>A special type of oxygen is saturated with chemical properties. Allows the patient to abandon oxygen for a relatively long period. Useful as an emergency medicine for travelers.</entitydescription.antioxygenlow>
  <entityname.antiaddiction>Reductorin</entityname.antiaddiction>
  <entitydescription.antiaddiction>An unusual medicine based on plasma and an organ of a marine inhabitant. Effectively treats the addiction of patients, but intensifies its withdrawal.</entitydescription.antiaddiction>
  <!-- Buffs -->
  <afflictionname.fluresistance>Persistance</afflictionname.fluresistance>
  <afflictiondescription.fluresistance>It seems that no disease, for a while, can so simply overcome the patient.</afflictiondescription.fluresistance>
  <afflictionname.spacerabiesresistance>Vaccinated</afflictionname.spacerabiesresistance>
  <afflictiondescription.spacerabiesresistance>Through an astronomical increase in the total number of white blood cells in the patient's body using substances, it is temporarily resistant to cosmic rabies.</afflictiondescription.spacerabiesresistance>
  <afflictionname.psyshockresistance>Iron psyche</afflictionname.psyshockresistance>
  <afflictiondescription.psyshockresistance>The patient is protected against psychotic shock temporarily.</afflictiondescription.psyshockresistance>
  <afflictionname.metabolismarrest>Metabolism arrest</afflictionname.metabolismarrest>
  <afflictiondescription.metabolismarrest>The patient is in a deep trance, and his metabolism has stopped almost completely.</afflictiondescription.metabolismarrest>
  <!-- Imported from "Skill n Drugs" by JaxMesa(29.12.25) -->
  <!-- Medicine -->
  <entityname.antibleedingacid>Hemofusive Acid</entityname.antibleedingacid>
  <entitydescription.antibleedingacid>A powerful coagulant compound that rapidly promotes blood clotting. Effectively treats severe bleeding but should be used with caution in patients with clotting disorders.</entitydescription.antibleedingacid>
  <entityname.antidrunk>Sobrix</entityname.antidrunk>
  <entitydescription.antidrunk>A fast-acting sobriety agent that rapidly metabolizes alcohol and clears the patient's system. Commonly used by crew members who need to return to duty quickly.</entitydescription.antidrunk>
  <!-- Buffs -->
  <afflictionname.oxygenbuff>Enhanced Oxygenation</afflictionname.oxygenbuff> 
  <afflictiondescription.oxygenbuff>The patient's blood is saturated with oxygen-rich compounds, significantly reducing oxygen consumption for a limited time.</afflictiondescription.oxygenbuff>
</infotexts>